Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there?
Hold on for me!
On this long journey that
we've only barely begun!
Friendship, love, courage,
and a little bit of fun!
These are the things.
That even as the years go by?
We'll not ever vanish from our minds!
We are all pieces of
a single planet Earth!
Little by little we can
find each other's worth!
And as we see what sort of
form we're meant to take!
All of us know the wind will
always keep on blowing away!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Look through that wind to dry!
All the tears as you're bleeding!
The things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there?
Hold on for me!
All the tears you shed will help
you to become so much stronger!
All the tears you shed
will help you to remember!
Everything, everything, everything!
Now and forever!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, yay!
Feel the wind, feel it surround you!
As you finish what you've begun!
Let's do that wind to dry all the tears!
As you're blaming the
things you must overcome!
Join the quest, join the adventure!
Found in meeting somebody new!
We'll never stop for anything!
Now that I see that you're
up ahead waiting there?
Hold on for me!
You can't be human!
What the heck are you?!
Nobody survives magellan's poison!
This is straight up!
Bonkers!
Just 20 hours then he
walked out on his own!
It's a miracle!
It has to be miracle!
Well, it's something far
greater than just that.
Straw Hat!
Straw Hat! It's Bon!
Glad to see you're alive! What?
Like I died?
Stop taking my chain!
You're the one who made me worry!
Straw Hat!
Hey, Bond! What's wrong?
He didn't die just now, did you?
Say something! Hey!
Bond boy is all worn out.
Better to let him rest.
Yo, what's up, Eva?
Show some respect!
Thanks, buddy.
That did the trick.
Oh, and thanks for helping out Bond, too.
Well, I do my best.
But I'm not the one
you should be thanking.
Bond boy worked hard for you. Huh?
Yes, I nudged you along
in the right direction.
And yes, my powers are
certainly wonderful.
But this one's the hero.
Bon Boy stayed with you all night long,
struggling and suffering for
hours and hours, never relenting.
He lost his voice.
He could barely stand.
He even spewed blood,
but he never stopped.
He shouted, hang in there, and
you have to live again and again.
Your recovery was far beyond miraculous.
I can only imagine that it's
thanks to all of his efforts.
I see
Wait a minute, is he naked?
Strawboy, I've come here to rescue you.
In the name of our everlasting friendship!
Thank you, Juan.
You're awesome!
I owe you my life.
I have your clothes, but I'm afraid
you're not ready to up and leave just yet.
It will take several days of rest and
recuperation before you're
back to your old self.
I don't have time for that!
I've already wasted too much!
Sorry to ask, but would you
mind looking after Bond for me?
I'll be back for him later.
Be careful, you see like he said
you've got some healing to do?
Looks like the paper still
pointing down ace is close.
By the way, where am I?
What's that thing?
It's a vivra card, I believe
But to answer your question, you're
on the floor between level 5 and 6.
I assume now you want to
go rescue your brother,
regardless of what
advice we might give you.
Well, it's your life after all.
You can do whatever you want with it.
Are you gonna make an escape too, Eva?
Before Bon and I got all messed up,
he was planning on breaking
your butt out of here.
Don't talk about his butt!
If you are gonna leave, can you show
me where Ace is on your way out?
Wait, what did you say?
Bond Boy sought out yours
truly to help rescue me.
Wow, how charming of him.
And a sweet gesture indeed.
But alas, I have no need to be saved.
It is not my time to break out just yet.
I know what's going on
in the world right now.
There's been a shift in the
tide and big changes are coming.
The Navy and the Whitebeard
Pirates are taking center stage.
Even so, the big man
still waiting things out.
I'm of course referring to my comrade,
the leader of all
revolutionaries in the world.
You may know
him as Dragon.
Oh, you're talking about my dad.
Yes, that's the plan.
When your dad makes a move
with that army of his,
then I shall do some
maneuvering of my own.
Call it my grand comeback tour.
If I were to escape from this place now,
I'd just end up on a sea of wanted lists.
Your dear papa and I never knew. Goodness.
Don't be ridiculous.
Dragon doesn't have any children.
That's just crazy talk.
Maybe I shouldn't have said anything.
Whatever.
Grandpa didn't keep it a secret.
The name of your father
is Monkey D. Dragon.
The revolutionary.
I don't really know that much about him.
I've never even seen
his face before. What?
But wait, this might be legit.
He doesn't come across as the
kind of person who would lie.
And he is a rather impressive
pirate in his own way.
Plus, the vitality he's shown
is the stuff of legends.
An extraordinary father
and an extraordinary son.
Please tell me, where
did you come from? Huh?
He's blue
Sage dragon when you step out for
air you always seem to face in the
same direction no matter where we go
do i i suppose i never gave it much
thought bit strange that you would
bring it up isn't it well i wondered
if it was some sort of homing instinct
you know the same thing animals have
thinking of home perhaps
some family in the east
maybe that's enough don't
stick your nose in my
past as you wish hang
on oh no if Straw Hat boy
really is dragon's son
this could be a disaster
Inazuma check to see when they're
taking ace boy away yes of
course there isn't much time The
fever card was pointing down,
which means he's still
here and still alive.
Thank goodness
Get me that info as soon as possible.
I'm heading to level six
with Straw Hat boy right now.
Yeah, you're really gonna show me the way
Hey, wait, you just said level six.
I thought Ace was on five
Actually, you're already below level five
Okay, whatever.
All right, let's go.
I Straw Hat Boy is Dragon's son as
he claims, then that means so is Ace.
Is this why the Navy captured
him and planned his execution?
But that's ludicrous,
not to mention suicidal.
There's no way they'd pick a fight with
Whitebeard Dragon at the same time.
What does the world government
hope to gain from all this?
In any case, I have no
choice but to make my move.
Bon, rest.
I'll be back later, okay?
Straw Hat Boy!
Listen closely.
You need to keep that a secret.
Do not let people know
that Dragon's your father.
Yeah, I just figured that out.
I'm his dear friend, as well as
one of his trusted commanders.
That means I'm a revolutionary.
That's the reason I was arrested.
So it's my duty to help you,
whether you like it or not.
I can't just stand around and let
my friend's son die before my eyes.
Listen up!
Tell everyone in the
newcomer land We're going to
move fast and rescue Ace
Boy before his execution?
And then we'll break out of Impel Down!
Does everyone understand? Woo!
It's so sudden!
I don't know if I'm ready.
A crossroad in life comes without warning.
If you're prepared to fight,
then be prepared to die.
All right then, let's do it!
Alright!
I'm coming to save you, Ace!
Now let's go!
His pulse is...
just fine.
That's not funny!
Empire...
Energy hormone!
It's a matter of adrenaline I just injected
you with enough of it for a full day
Just to let you know you're going
to feel the side effects several
days from now but by that Point
let's hope it won't really matter
Mr Two Mr Three and Buggy the Clown
Mr.
Two just waltzed them into the freezing
hell, and that was the last you saw of them?
Yes, that's right.
His disguise was perfect, sir.
We searched for them, but all we could
find was that head brisk covered in blood.
From the lack of remains, we assumed
that they took Straw Hat out of the cell,
but were eaten up by the wolves afterward.
I see.
Look at me,
sitting in the warden's chair, wearing
his special order headpiece thing,
and yet I feel so empty. You know why?
Because I haven't earned it
until I've crushed Magellan.
Right, good luck with that.
And let me remind you, if we
get tricked or beaten again,
not only the warden's job, but
your job will be on the line.
My position, too?
You're late, sir.
And you're strict, Domino.
Try to empty your bowels faster next time.
Not possible.
Not again you'll have to
hold it in if we don't
make it in time we'll ruin
the reputation of Impel!
Down all
right listen
up our mission is to take
custody of Port Custody
Ace and then transfer
him to the Marine Board
Navy Headquarters got it
until the moment that we
hand over that prisoner?
I need each and every
one of you on full alert.
Yes, sir!
That we're ready for any possibility?
We're moving him in a convoy of five ships
under the direction of five vice-admerals.
We cannot afford a single slip-up.
Understood, sir!
I don't know why, but I
got a crap ton of energy!
Good.
You're going to need it.
We can't afford to waste even a second.
There's no security here.
So flex those leg muscles and
run like crazy, Straw Hat boy!
Nothing can stop us.
Hey, what's going on over there?
Who are those weirdos?
Ivankov? No way!
I thought he was dead.
No, it can't be.
I'm out of my way!
No time for you!
Death?
Wee!
Inazuma, open it up!
Right.
They'll be monitoring us from
now on. Who cares? Let them come!
We have intruders!
They're running down the staircase
between level five and six.
Wait, the guy with the big head.
He's that queen of the queers
that went missing years ago.
Named Zivankov.
Where's he been hiding?
We gave up on that guy ages ago.
The one running next to
him is Straw Hat Luffy.
I thought the warden took care of
him, but he looks as healthy as ever.
The third one is another missing prisoner.
Inazuma, a revolutionary
from the South Blue.
What the hell is going on?
Looks like they're heading
straight for level six.
I think they're trying
to save Firefist Ace.
Domino and Warden
Magellan are also on their
way to level six for the
transfer as we speak.
They're all going to bump into each other.
How can they all still be alive?
Vice Warden, when do you get here?
Activate the passageway
trapped immediately.
Call all the jailers on level six.
Tell them to get ready.
They'll need to stand
their ground until Mistress
Sadie and the Demon Guards
arrive as reinforcements.
Report everything that's going on
to all floors in Warden Magellan.
You have your orders
get moving right yes sir
i've never seen the vice
warden so serious before?
Maybe it's the imposter again we
have to stop these troublemakers!
Since i can't blame the
warden for this one i mean
We can make it we can make it.
Hang on, Ace!
I'm coming for you!
This is it, Crocus D. Ace.
You're going to be
transferred to Marineford.
Upon your arrival there, you will
be taken to the execution grounds.
The End
Straw Hat Luffy, Yvonne Conf, Queen of
the Queers, and Inazuma the Revolutionary.
All three criminals are
now entering level six.
What are we going to do?
Ace!
This one?
He's gone!
Are you absolutely certain
that this is the right cell?
Yes, I promise you.
He was just here, I swear.
We're a bit late, it seems.
A Straw Hat?
Then it's him.
It must be.
She said that my brother is here.
She was telling the truth.
I never thought anyone could
penetrate this fortress,
let alone make it all
the way to level six.
You there.
You're Straw Hat, aren't you? Yeah.
You're a moment late. He was here.
They took him to the elevator
for the prison transfer.
Go.
There's still a chance you can catch them.
Thanks, but who are you?
My goodness. It's you.
Thanks for the help, whoever you are.
Who is this boy?
To brave the impossible!
To accomplish the inconceivable!
And to charge into yet another struggle!
More hopeless than the last!
They took that elevator
to the upper floor.
Let's go!
Thankfully they've left the gate open.
Nice!
Seems the operation system is locked up.
It won't budge!
That sucks!
All right!
We'll just have to climb up.
There's no other way.
Do it, sir.
Oh, man, that was close.
Ah, I see.
They can't let things be
convenient for us now, can they?
We'll just have to find
ourselves another way.
They're watching us.
Let's go back to the stairs.
Hey those jerks blocked the
staircase they're trying to
trap us we'll just have to
break through then won't we?
That's an awful lot of gas
do you think it's deadly?
I don't know who the hell
you punts are but if you're
gonna get yourselves killed
don't take us with you!
Shut up!
Nobody cares.
It doesn't matter if it's poisonous.
I gotta go!
Wait!
Well, there you have it.
Sleeping gas.
The boy didn't even give
it a second thought.
At least try to stay alive.
Get out of here already.
Move!
This is the last thing we need.
I see.
They're hoping to stop us without a fight.
How cowardly.
Vice Warden, level six is
now blocked off completely.
The sleeping gas is highly effective
and there's nowhere to run.
Just in case, keep the guards on standby.
Did you report all this to Warden
Magellan? Yes, sir. Just now.
Good.
That means I get to keep my job.
Now to place the blame for
this entire fiasco on Magellan.
Then I'll become the warden.
Sir, the microphone's still on.
Come on, man!
What do you know?
Straw Hat made it to level
six just after we left.
Unfortunate timing for you.
Luffy!
I wasn't in the mood for a nap,
but it seems we're out of options.
It's all over.
The emergency sleeping
gas has flooded level 6.
It's only a matter of time
before they catch Straw Hat.
Apparently the freezing hell
wasn't punishment enough for him.
Since the cell you are in now
as a vacancy Straw Hat will have
a taste of the torment reserved
for our most heinous criminals.
Luffy, no one told you
to stop, keep walking.
I assure you, resistance is futile.
Luffy!
Your brother's a pirate.
His fate was sealed the moment
he stepped in this prison.
Damn it, Luffy.
I'd hoped Hancock was lying.
But this troubles me.
No matter how strong he is, he
shouldn't have recovered from my poison.
And so quickly.
How did you do it, Straw Hat?
How did you survive?
Come on, do something!
The whole floor is filling with gas!
Who the hell is this guy?
He's cutting a stone floor
like it's made of paper!
Huh?
Now he's flipping it up like a ribbon!
Well, that's one way to deal
with the problem, I suppose.
I don't get it, but I like it.
Inazuma ate the snip-snip fruit,
so now he's a scissor man.
He can manipulate whatever he
cuts as though it's made of paper.
Really?
That's cool
Don't fall asleep!
If you doze off on me,
I might get drowsy But I never sleep!
Stop doing that!
Good morning.
We gotta keep going up, crab guy.
Thanks for blocking out the gas, but now
I can't go up the stairs to get to Ace.
This is the only way to prevent the
sleeping gas from filling up the room.
If you're unconscious, you
can't save anybody, can you?
I'll save him whether
I'm unconscious or not!
I'm not gonna let him die, you understand?
Don't be ridiculous.
It was a simple plan, but
it defeated us nonetheless.
As much as I hate to admit it,
we're trapped here on Level 6,
at least for the time being.
Sorry, buddy.
Well, this is all I can do.
At least the jerks can't watch us now.
Well, we gave it a good shot,
but no time for regrets.
I'm sure that by now
they've made their way to
the top floor to hand
off Ace for the transfer.
Even if we could get out, we'd have quite
the melange of obstacles in our way.
The Navy's convoy is quick, too.
Take a look at the Viva card.
It's not pointing straight
up anymore, is it?
That means that Ace has already
been handed over to the Navy.
Come on, it's time to start
thinking of ourselves.
The first step is your escape, I promise.
I will do my very best to break
you out of this prison safely.
As far as Ace Boy in the Navy goes,
that ship has already sailed, literally.
Give up on him, okay?
Or rather, put your faith in Whitebeard.
There's no way he'd give
up on one of his own.
He'll come up with something.
I'm leaving. Huh?
I'm going to Marineford.
Don't be stupid!
A massive battle is about
to take place between
two of the most powerful
forces in the entire world.
Do you have any idea how
strong Whitebeard is?
What about all the admirals, vice-admirals,
and the warlords on the Navy side?
Remember them?
And are you also forgetting how close to
death you were after
the fight with Magellan?
Do you have that many lives to spare?
What is it?
Look, if I give up now, I'll regret it.
I know that face I've
seen it many times before
it's the face of his father staring at me.
Unflinching you can do
as you like but first
of all how do you propose
we get off this floor?
If you want out that bat
then set me free I'll
make a hole in the ceiling
and you'll be free to go.
Sound good no way they've
got him down here too
just like
old times huh
you know for the life of me.
I couldn't think of a good reason to break
out of here but whitebeard and the navy
are gonna Start a war this is my chance to
bring down that old man once and for all.
This clash of powers
has piqued my interest,
and I've just the tools in my disposal
to get us a front row seat to the action.
You scratch my back
and I'll scratch yours.
Not a bad proposition, is it?
Screw that crap!
You messed up Phoebe's
whole country, you jerk!
You can rock down here!
That was a long time ago.
That place is no longer
of any interest to me.
however you may feel we still need
his help if we have an opportunity
to escape from here then we're
obliged to take it what are you crazy
eva do you know what this guy is no
time to be hoity-toity sandy pants
here is our only ticket outside hello
ifon cough my my it's been a long
time a Krieg boy hey wait you two
know each other just a passing
acquaintance i met him when he was a
rookie all wet behind the ears i wouldn't
worry if this guy tries to double
cross us i'll whip him into shape in
a jiffy as long as i've got an eye on
him then he should behave just fine
he is a scoundrel but
he's a scoundrel with
a weakness i know well
hey if you so much as
mention a word you can
shut that mouth of yours
help us out and keep
your dirty little secret
Hee-haw!
Cocky bastard.
Hey, you guys, while you're at it,
you should let me out of here, too.
Me, too, me, too.
I got a boat to pick with whitebeard.
Yeah, let me out, too.
Shut up.
Death wing.
Please, have mercy on me.
i beg you to take me with you i will
be of great service i've known your
brother ace since he first joined
the white beard pirates he's a good
friend and i know you too from all
the stories he's told i'm not like
the others down here i was arrested
because i objected to his execution
I want to help save Ace too I swear
I will put my life on the line
for him Hmm Jean Bay The first son
of the sea If they imprisoned him
here Then he must have relinquished
his title As one of the seven
warlords That would mean his self-proclaimed
bond with Ace Has merit indeed
Alright then Wait, are you sure?
You've never even met this man,
and he's most assuredly dangerous.
It'll be fine.
Just let him out, okay?
You have my gratitude. Me next!
I like Ace too!
I'll die for him and stuff!
You boys are asking for a death!
two warlords or two former
warlords that is wait a second
this guy for real you won't
regret this i will fight to
protect ace even if it means
my own end if you think you
can stop the war between the
navy and whitebeard go ahead
and try i don't give a damn
either way as long as i get
a shot at that crusty old
bastard it's worth it for me if
you think i'll let you lay a
single finger on white beard
you're wrong well then why
don't you just try and stop me
Krieg boy your secret past remember
it's settled then let's get moving
we don't have much time with
a team this formidable not even
impel down can hold us Hee-haw!